Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series LXXIV. WAGES
  - Sub-Series 408-188. Wages
    - Chicago Union Station Company. Mediation Case No. A-4530., 1954-1961 (Box 565, Folder 42)
    - Chicago Union Station Company. Mediation Case No. A-4530. Proceedings. Volume 1., 1955 (Box 566, Folder 1)
      1955 April 11
    - Chicago Union Station Company. Mediation Case No. A-4530. Proceedings. Volume 2, 1955 (Box 566, Folder 2)
      1955 April 12
    - Chicago Union Station Company. Mediation Case No. A-4530. Proceedings. Volume 3, 1955 (Box 566, Folder 3)
      1955 April 13
    - Chicago Union Station Company. Mediation Case No. A-4530. Proceedings. Volume 4, 1955 (Box 566, Folder 4)
      1955 April 15
    - Chicago Union Station Company. Mediation Case No. A-4530. Exhibits, 1955 (Box 566, Folder 5)
    - Chicago Union Station Company. Mediation Case No. A-4530. Employees` Exhibits, 1955 (Box 566, Folder 6)
    - Chicago Union Station Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 566, Folder 7)
    - Chicago Union Station Company. Mediation Case No. A-5101. Rates of Pay for Ticket Sellers, 1956-1958 (Box 566, Folder 8)
    - Chicago Union Station Company. Mediation Case No. A-5101. Proceedings. Volume 1., 1956 (Box 566, Folder 9)
      1956 July 23
    - Chicago Union Station Company. Mediation Case No. A-5101. Proceedings. Volume 2, 1956 (Box 566, Folder 10)
      1956 July 24
    - Chicago Union Station Company. Mediation Case No. A-5101. Proceedings. Volume 3, 1956 (Box 566, Folder 11)
      1956 July 25
    - Chicago Union Station Company. Mediation Case No. A-5101. Exhibits, 1956 (Box 566, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 408-190. Wages
    - Duluth Union Depot and Transfer Company. General, 1937-1951 (Box 566, Folder 13)
    - Duluth Union Depot and Transfer Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 566, Folder 14)
    - Duluth Union Depot and Transfer Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 566, Folder 15)
    - Duluth Union Depot and Transfer Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 566, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 408-191. Wages
    - Boston Terminal Company. General, 1931-1951 (Box 566, Folder 17)
    - Boston Terminal Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 566, Folder 18)
    - Boston Terminal Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 566, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 408-192. Wages
    - Northern Pacific Terminal Company of Oregon. General, 1932-1951 (Box 566, Folder 20)
    - Northern Pacific Terminal Company of Oregon. Mediation Case No. A-2344, 1945-1947 (Box 566, Folder 21)
    - Northern Pacific Terminal Company of Oregon. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 566, Folder 22)
    - Northern Pacific Terminal Company of Oregon. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 566, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 408-194. Wages
    - Atlanta Terminal Company. General, 1934-1955 (Box 566, Folder 24)
    - Atlanta Terminal Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 566, Folder 25)
    - Atlanta Terminal Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 567, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 408-195. Wages
    - City Bus Company, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma. General, 1953 (Box 567, Folder 2)
    - City Bus Company, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma. General, 1938-1952 (Box 567, Folder 3)
    - City Bus Company, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 567, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 408-196. Wages
    - Union Terminal Company of Dallas. General, 1952-1956 (Box 567, Folder 5)
    - Union Terminal Company of Dallas. General, 1945-1951 (Box 567, Folder 6)
    - Union Terminal Company of Dallas. Agreements. Clerks and Red Caps. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 567, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 408-198. Wages
    - Detroit and Toledo Shore Line Railroad. General, 1944-1951 (Box 567, Folder 8)
    - Detroit and Toledo Shore Line Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 567, Folder 9)
    - Detroit and Toledo Shore Line Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 567, Folder 10)
    - Detroit and Toledo Shore Line Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 567, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 408-200. Wages
    - Texarkana Union Station Trust Company. General, 1933-1951 (Box 567, Folder 12)
    - Texarkana Union Station Trust Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 567, Folder 13)
    - Texarkana Union Station Trust Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 567, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 408-202. Wages
    - Pueblo Union Depot and Railroad Company. General, 1935-1953 (Box 567, Folder 15)
    - Pueblo Union Depot and Railroad Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 567, Folder 16)
    - Pueblo Union Depot and Railroad Company. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 567, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 408-204. Wages
    - Tulsa Union Depot. General, 1932-1953 (Box 567, Folder 18)
    - Tulsa Union Depot. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 567, Folder 19)
    - Tulsa Union Depot. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 567, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 408-205. Wages
    - Union Inland Freight Station. General, 1947-1951 (Box 567, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 408-206. Wages
    - Fort Worth Belt Railway. General, 1932-1951 (Box 567, Folder 22)
    - Fort Worth Belt Railway Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 567, Folder 23)
    - Fort Worth Belt Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 567, Folder 24)
    - Fort Worth Belt Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 567, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 408-207. Wages
    - Cincinnati Union Terminal. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 567, Folder 26)
    - Cincinnati Union Terminal. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 567, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 408-209. Wages
    - Monongahela Railway Company. General, 1937-1951 (Box 567, Folder 28)
    - Monongahela Railway Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 567, Folder 29)
    - Monongahela Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 567, Folder 30)
    - Monongahela Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 567, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 408-210. Wages
    - Interstate Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement. Mediation Case No. A-7065, 1963-1965 (Box 567, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 408-211. Wages
    - St. Joseph Union Depot. General, 1948-1953 (Box 567, Folder 33)
    - St. Joseph Union Depot. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 567, Folder 34)
    - St. Joseph Union Depot. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 567, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 408-212. Wages
    - Piedmont and Northern Railway. General, 1945-1953 (Box 567, Folder 36)
    - Piedmont and Northern Railway. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 567, Folder 37)
    - Piedmont and Northern Railway. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 567, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 408-214. Wages
    - Duluth, Winnipeg, and Pacific Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 567, Folder 39)
    - Duluth, Winnipeg, and Pacific Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 567, Folder 40)
    - Duluth, Winnipeg, and Pacific Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 567, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 408-215. Wages
    - New Orleans Public Belt Railroad. General, 1944-1950 (Box 567, Folder 42)
    - New Orleans Public Belt Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 568, Folder 1)
    - New Orleans Public Belt Railroad. Mediation Case No. A-6034, 1959 (Box 568, Folder 2)
    - New Orleans Public Belt Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 568, Folder 3)
    - New Orleans Public Belt Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 568, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 408-216. Wages
    - Illinois Terminal Railroad. General, 1945-1953 (Box 568, Folder 5)
    - Illinois Terminal Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 568, Folder 6)
    - Illinois Terminal Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 568, Folder 7)
    - Illinois Terminal Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 568, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 408-217. Wages
    - Albany Passenger Terminal Company, Savannah, Georgia. General, 1954-1955 (Box 568, Folder 9)
    - Albany Passenger Terminal Company, Savannah, Georgia. General, 1935-1953 (Box 568, Folder 10)
    - Albany Passenger Terminal Company, Savannah, Georgia. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 568, Folder 11)
    - Albany Passenger Terminal Company, Savannah, Georgia. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 568, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 408-218. Wages
    - St. Joseph Terminal Railroad Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 568, Folder 13)
    - St. Joseph Terminal Railroad Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 568, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 408-220. Wages
    - Chicago, South Shore, and South Bend Railroad. General, 1944-1953 (Box 568, Folder 15)
    - Chicago, South Shore, and South Bend Railroad.1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 568, Folder 16)
    - Chicago, South Shore, and South Bend Railroad.1955 Wage Movement (Box 568, Folder 17)
    - Chicago, South Shore, and South Bend Railroad. Agreements. Clerical, Office Station, and Storehouse Employees; Concession and Commissary Employees. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 568, Folder 18)
    - Chicago, South Shore, and South Bend Railroad.40-Hour Week. Concession Department, 1949-1951 (Box 568, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 408-221. Wages
    - Pacific Electric Railway. General, 1946-1953 (Box 568, Folder 20)
    - Pacific Electric Railway. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 568, Folder 21)
    - Pacific Electric Railway. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 568, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 408-222. Wages
    - Fort Street Union Depot, Detroit, Michigan. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 568, Folder 23)
    - Fort Street Union Depot, Detroit, Michigan. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 568, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 408-223. Wages
    - Minneapolis, Northfield, and Southern Railway Company. General, 1934-1953 (Box 568, Folder 25)
    - Minneapolis, Northfield, and Southern Railway Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 568, Folder 26)
    - Minneapolis, Northfield, and Southern Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 568, Folder 27)
    - Minneapolis, Northfield, and Southern Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 568, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 408-225. Wages
    - Western Fruit Express Company. General, 1944-1953 (Box 568, Folder 29)
    - Western Fruit Express Company. General, 1954-1955 (Box 568, Folder 30)
    - Western Fruit Express Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 568, Folder 31)
    - Western Fruit Express Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 568, Folder 32)
    - Western Fruit Express Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 568, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 408-227. Wages
    - Universal Carloading and Distributing Company. Wage Increase Case Before National War Labor Board Covering Employees of Both Universal Carloading and National Carloading Corporation, 1942-1944 (Box 568, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 408-228. Wages
    - Wichita Union Terminal. General, 1937-1953 (Box 568, Folder 35)
    - Wichita Union Terminal. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 568, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 408-230. Wages
    - Akron, Canton, and Youngstown Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 568, Folder 37)
    - Akron, Canton, and Youngstown Railroad. General, 1954 (Box 568, Folder 38)
    - Akron, Canton, and Youngstown Railroad. General, 1936-1953 (Box 569, Folder 1)
    - Akron, Canton, and Youngstown Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 569, Folder 2)
    - Akron, Canton, and Youngstown Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 569, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 408-231. Wages
    - Harbor Belt Line Railroad, Los Angeles, California. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1964 (Box 569, Folder 4)
    - Harbor Belt Line Railroad, Los Angeles, California. General, 1937-1954 (Box 569, Folder 5)
    - Harbor Belt Line Railroad, Los Angeles, California. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 569, Folder 6)
    - Harbor Belt Line Railroad, Los Angeles, California. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 569, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 408-232. Wages
    - Union Belt Railway of Detroit, Michigan. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 569, Folder 8)
    - Union Belt Railway of Detroit, Michigan. General, 1937-1953 (Box 569, Folder 9)
    - Union Belt Railway of Detroit, Michigan. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 569, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 408-233. Wages
    - Clinchfield Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 569, Folder 11)
    - Clinchfield Railroad. General, 1937-1953 (Box 569, Folder 12)
    - Clinchfield Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 569, Folder 13)
    - Clinchfield Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 569, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 408-234. Wages
    - Alton and Southern Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 569, Folder 15)
    - Alton and Southern Railroad. General, 1936-1951 (Box 569, Folder 16)
    - Alton and Southern Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 569, Folder 17)
    - Alton and Southern Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 569, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 408-235. Wages
    - Chicago and Illinois Western Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 569, Folder 19)
    - Chicago and Illinois Western Railroad. General, 1937-1953 (Box 569, Folder 20)
    - Chicago and Illinois Western Railroad. General, 1955 (Box 569, Folder 21)
    - Chicago and Illinois Western Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 569, Folder 22)
    - Chicago and Illinois Western Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 569, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 408-237. Wages
    - Atlantic and East Carolina Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement. Mediation Case No. A-7059, 1963-1965 (Box 569, Folder 24)
    - Atlantic and East Carolina Railroad. General, 1952-1958 (Box 569, Folder 25)
    - Atlantic and East Carolina Railroad. General, 1947-1951 (Box 569, Folder 26)
    - Atlantic and East Carolina Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 569, Folder 27)
    - Atlantic and East Carolina Railroad. Mediation Case No. A-3955, 1951-1952 (Box 569, Folder 28)
    - Atlantic and East Carolina Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 569, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 408-238. Wages
    - Burlington-Rock Island Railroad and Joint Texas Division of Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railway and Fort Worth and Denver City Railway. General, 1952 (Box 569, Folder 30)
    - Burlington-Rock Island Railroad and Joint Texas Division of Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railway and Fort Worth and Denver City Railway. General, 1932-1951 (Box 569, Folder 31)
    - Burlington-Rock Island Railroad and Joint Texas Division of Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railway and Fort Worth and Denver City Railway. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 569, Folder 32)
    - Burlington-Rock Island Railroad and Joint Texas Division of Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railway and Fort Worth and Denver City Railway. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 569, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 408-239. Wages
    - Chicago Tunnel Company. General, 1953-1959 (Box 569, Folder 34)
    - Chicago Tunnel Company. General, 1945-1952 (Box 569, Folder 35)
    - Chicago Tunnel Company. Chicago Terminal Company. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 569, Folder 36)
    - Chicago Tunnel Company. Chicago Terminal Company. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 569, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 408-240. Wages
    - Alameda Belt Line. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 569, Folder 38)
    - Alameda Belt Line. General, 1937-1953 (Box 569, Folder 39)
    - Alameda Belt Line. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 569, Folder 40)
    - Alameda Belt Line. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 569, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 408-241. Wages
    - Canadian National Railways, Newfoundland Division. General, 1936-1956 (Box 570, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 408-243. Wages
    - Port Terminal Railroad Association. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 570, Folder 2)
    - Port Terminal Railroad Association. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement. General, 1938-1951 (Box 570, Folder 3)
    - Port Terminal Railroad Association. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 570, Folder 4)
    - Port Terminal Railroad Association. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 570, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 408-244. Wages
    - San Diego and Arizona Eastern Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 570, Folder 6)
    - San Diego and Arizona Eastern Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 570, Folder 7)
    - San Diego and Arizona Eastern Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 570, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 408-247. Wages
    - Pacific Car Demurrage Bureau. General, 1937-1953 (Box 570, Folder 9)
    - Pacific Car Demurrage Bureau. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 570, Folder 10)
    - Pacific Car Demurrage Bureau. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 570, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 408-248. Wages
    - Chicago Produce Terminal Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 570, Folder 12)
    - Chicago Produce Terminal Company. General, 1923-1953 (Box 570, Folder 13)
    - Chicago Produce Terminal Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 570, Folder 14)
    - Chicago Produce Terminal Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 570, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 408-252. Wages
    - Jay Street Terminal Company, Brooklyn, New York. General, 1937-1957 (Box 570, Folder 16)
    - Jay Street Terminal Company, Brooklyn, New York. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 570, Folder 17)
    - Jay Street Terminal Company, Brooklyn, New York. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 570, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 408-253. Wages
    - Sacramento Northern Railway. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 570, Folder 19)
    - Sacramento Northern Railway. General, 1947-1954 (Box 570, Folder 20)
    - Sacramento Northern Railway. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 570, Folder 21)
    - Sacramento Northern Railway. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 570, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 408-256. Wages
    - Union Island Freight Station. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 570, Folder 23)
    - Union Island Freight Station. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 570, Folder 24)
    - Union Island Freight Station. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 570, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 408-257. Wages
    - Wichita Falls and Southern Railway. General, 1945-1952 (Box 570, Folder 26)
    - Wichita Falls and Southern Railway. Mediation Case No. A-3165, 1949-1950 (Box 570, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 408-259. Wages
    - Chicago and Illinois Midland Railway Company. General, 1946-1954 (Box 570, Folder 28)
    - Chicago and Illinois Midland Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 570, Folder 29)
    - Chicago and Illinois Midland Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 570, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 408-261. Wages
    - Litchfield and Madison Railway Company. General, 1950-1959 (Box 570, Folder 31)
    - Litchfield and Madison Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 570, Folder 32)
    - Litchfield and Madison Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 570, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 408-263. Wages
    - Southern Pacific de Mexico. General, 1941-1951 (Box 570, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 408-267. Wages
    - Ontario Northland Railway. General, 1941-1954 (Box 570, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 408-268. Wages
    - Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern Railway Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 570, Folder 36)
    - Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern Railway Company. General, 1955-1961 (Box 571, Folder 1)
    - Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern Railway Company. General, 1932-1954 (Box 571, Folder 2)
    - Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 571, Folder 3)
    - Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 571, Folder 4)
    - Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern Railway Company. Mediation Case No. A-5185. Walkie-Talkie, 1956-1959 (Box 571, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 408-269. Wages
    - Tennessee Central Railway Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 571, Folder 6)
    - Tennessee Central Railway Company. General, 1939-1952 (Box 571, Folder 7)
    - Tennessee Central Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 571, Folder 8)
    - Tennessee Central Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 571, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 408-270. Wages
    - Detroit Terminal Railroad. General, 1937-1951 (Box 571, Folder 10)
    - Detroit Terminal Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 571, Folder 11)
    - Detroit Terminal Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 571, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 408-272. Wages
    - Pacific Fruit Express Company. General, 1946-1953 (Box 571, Folder 13)
    - Pacific Fruit Express Company. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 571, Folder 14)
    - Pacific Fruit Express Company. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 571, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 408-273. Wages
    - H. Harris Company. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 571, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 408-277. Wages
    - East St. Louis Relay Depot Passenger Station Association. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 571, Folder 17)
    - East St. Louis Relay Depot Passenger Station Association. General, 1937-1954 (Box 571, Folder 18)
    - East St. Louis Relay Depot Passenger Station Association. General, 1955 (Box 571, Folder 19)
    - East St. Louis Relay Depot Passenger Station Association. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 571, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 408-278. Wages
    - New York Dock Railway. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 571, Folder 21)
    - New York Dock Railway. General, 1937-1951 (Box 571, Folder 22)
    - New York Dock Railway. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 571, Folder 23)
    - New York Dock Railway. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 571, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 408-279. Wages
    - Baltimore Steam Packet Company. General, 1943-1951 (Box 571, Folder 25)
    - Baltimore Steam Packet Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 571, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 408-280. Wages
    - Port Utilities Commission, Charleston, South Carolina. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 571, Folder 27)
    - Port Utilities Commission, Charleston, South Carolina. Port Terminal Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 571, Folder 28)
    - Port Utilities Commission, Charleston, South Carolina. 1955 Wage Movement., 1955-1956 (Box 571, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 408-282. Wages
    - Pennsylvania-Reading Seashore Lines. General, 1938-1951 (Box 571, Folder 30)
    - Pennsylvania-Reading Seashore Lines. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 571, Folder 31)
    - Pennsylvania-Reading Seashore Lines. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 571, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 408-286. Wages
    - Boston Market Terminal Company. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 571, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 408-287. Wages
    - Brooklyn Eastern District Terminal. General, 1939-1951 (Box 571, Folder 34)
    - Brooklyn Eastern District Terminal. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 571, Folder 35)
    - Brooklyn Eastern District Terminal. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 571, Folder 36)
    - Brooklyn Eastern District Terminal. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 571, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 408-288. Wages
    - Wichita Union Terminal Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 571, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 408-289. Wages
    - Dallas Car Interchange and Inspection Bureau. General, 1950-1956 (Box 572, Folder 1)
    - Dallas Car Interchange and Inspection Bureau. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 572, Folder 2)
    - Dallas Car Interchange and Inspection Bureau. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 572, Folder 3)
    - Dallas Car Interchange and Inspection Bureau. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 572, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 408-290. Wages
    - Pacific Coast Railway Company. General, 1950-1955 (Box 572, Folder 5)
    - Pacific Coast Railway Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 572, Folder 6)
    - Pacific Coast Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 572, Folder 7)
    - Pacific Coast Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 572, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 408-294. Wages
    - Troy Union Railroad Company. General, 1937-1951 (Box 572, Folder 9)
    - Troy Union Railroad Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 572, Folder 10)
    - Troy Union Railroad Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 572, Folder 11)
    - Troy Union Railroad Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 572, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 408-295. Wages
    - Union Terminal Railway, St. Joseph, Missouri. General, 1950-1954 (Box 572, Folder 13)
    - Union Terminal Railway, St. Joseph, Missouri. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 572, Folder 14)